iconpeak.com 2015-06-07

# Iconpeak - Mobile Advertising

### Privacy policy

Iconpeak is committed to protecting the privacy of internet users. This Privacy Policy explains the underlying purpose and applied procedures of our data collection and processing. We adhere to industry guidelines and applicable laws and will continue to review and improve our procedures to ensure the protection of consumer privacy. We may change our Privacy Policy at any time and recommend you to visit our website on a regular basis in order to have the most recent version.

Personal information is all data that can be referred to a natural person who is alive, including the name, mailing address, email address, phone number, date of birth etc.

### Data

For security purposes our web servers temporarily record the connection details of incoming requests, the page that you visited and that may have referred you to us, the duration of your visit as well as the characteristics of your internet browser and operating system.

Our websites may include anonymous analytics software to identify usage patterns. These tools do not collect any personal information. They collect data in an anonymized and aggregated format for statistical purposes and the improvement of our services.

We use our own proprietary technology to serve and measure the delivery of our ads. For that we may place and/or read so-called "cookies” on the device's of internet users under any subdomain of iconpeak.com. Both our temporary and persistent cookies do not store any personal information. Anyone may delete and/or block our cookies in their browser at any time.

Advertisers and publishers having a contractual agreement with Iconpeak have agreed to the collection and processing of certain personal information upon registration. Their personal information is used to provide access to the requested products and services, respond to incoming enquiries, process payments, and any other purpose that they have consented to or which is allowed under applicable law. They are entitled to withdraw their consent to process personal information that they have provided to us at any time. We do not sell any personal information of our business partners.
